<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyRecylerView</string>
    <string name="heroes_name">Nama Pahlawan</string>
    <string name="hero_nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="desc">Hero desc</string>
    <string name="herobirth">Hero birthday</string>
    <string name="detail">Detail</string>
    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="grid">Grid</string>
    <string name="with_cardview">with CardView</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="share">detail</string>

    <string name="content_text">Albedo — an alchemist based in Mondstadt, in the service of the Knights of Favonius.
Genius, Kreideprinz, or Captain of the Investigation Team. Such titles and honors are of no consequence to him when there is so much more research to conduct.
The pursuit of fortune and connections cannot hold a candle to his hearts desire — acquiring the limitless, obscure knowledge left behind by previous generations of scholars.</string>
    <string name="content_specs_display">september 13th</string>
    <string name="content_specs_size">Mondstadt</string>
    <string name="content_specs_battery">Knights of Favonius</string>
    <string name="stock">The Kreideprinz</string>
    <string name="my_name">Nojima Kenji</string>
    <string name="dummy_value">Albedo</string>
    <string name="sword">Sword</string>

    <string name="vc">Voice Actor</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="nation">Nation</string>
    <string name="affil">Affiliation</string>

    <string name="bow">Bow</string>
    <string name="polearm">Polearm</string>
    <string name="catalyst">Catalyst</string>
    <string name="claymore">Claymore</string>
    
    <string name="amber">Amber</string>
    <string name="bennet">Bennet</string>
    <string name="diluc">Diluc</string>
    <string name="eula">Eula</string>
    <string name="jean">Jean</string>
    <string name="kaeya">Kaeya</string>
    <string name="noelle">Noelle</string>
    <string name="razor">Razor</string>
    <string name="sucrose">Sucrose</string>

    <string name="desc_amber">A perky, straightforward girl, who is also the only Outrider of the Knights of Favonius. Her amazing mastery of the glider has made her a three-time winner of the Gliding Championship in Mondstadt. As a rising star within the Knights of Favonius, Amber is always ready for any challenging tasks.</string>
    <string name="pang_amber">Outrider</string>
    <string name="amber_birthday">August 10th</string>
    <string name="amber_vc">Iwami Manaka</string>

    <string name="bennet_desc">The few young adventurers that the Mondstadt Adventurers Guild has always found themselves tangled up in baffling bouts of bad luck. He is the only active member of his own adventure group, known as "Benny'\s Adventure Team," after all the other members decided to "take leave" following a series of unfortunate incidents. As a result, the team is currently on the verge of being dissolved. Being unable to break the poor boys heart, Katheryne of the Adventurers Guild has kept "Benny Adventure Team" on the books, whilst also hiding from him the fact that all the other members have long since officially left the team.</string>
    <string name="pang_bennet">Trial by Fire</string>
    <string name="bennet_birthday">February 29th</string>
    <string name="bennet_affil">Adventures Guild</string>
    <string name="bennet_vc">Ousaka Ryouta</string>

    <string name="diluc_desc">As the wealthiest gentleman in Mondstadt, the ever-dapper Diluc always presents himself as the epitome of perfection. But behind the courteous visage burns a zealous soul that has sworn to protect Mondstadt at all costs, allowing him to mercilessly vanquish all who threaten his city.</string>
    <string name="pang_diluc">Darknight Hero</string>
    <string name="diluc_birthday">April 30th</string>
    <string name="diluc_affil">Dawn Winery</string>
    <string name="diluc_vc">Ono Kenshou</string>

    <string name="eula_desc">A rebellious descendant of the old aristocracy who is always out on the battlefield. As one born into the old aristocracy, carrying the bloodline of sinners, Eula has needed a unique approach to the world to navigate the towering walls of prejudice peacefully. Of course, this did not prevent her from severing ties with her clan. As the outstanding Spindrift Knight, she hunts down Mondstadts enemies in the wild to exact her unique "vengeance."</string>
    <string name="pang_eula">Spindrift</string>
    <string name="eula_birthday">October 25th</string>
    <string name="eula_affil">Knight of Favonius
    Lawrence Clan</string>
    <string name="eula_vc">Sato Rina</string>

    <string name="jean_desc">As the Acting Grand Master of the Knights, Jean has always been devoted to her duties and maintaining peace in Mondstadt. She had taken precautions long before the onset of Stormterrors assault, and she will guard Mondstadt with her life as always.</string>
    <string name="pang_jean">Dandellion Knight</string>
    <string name="jean_birthday">March 14th</string>
    <string name="jean_affil">Knight of Favonius
    Gunnhildr Clan</string>
    <string name="jean_vc">Saito Chiwa</string>

    <string name="kaeya_desc">In the Knights of Favonius, Kaeya is the most trusted aide for the Acting Grand Master Jean. You can always count on him to solve any intractable problems. Everyone in Mondstadt loves Kaeya, but no one knows what secrets this witty.</string>
    <string name="pang_Kaeya">Cavalry Captain</string>
    <string name="kaeya_birthday">November 30th</string>
    <string name="kaeya_affil">Knight of Favonius</string>
    <string name="kaeya_vc">Toriumi Kohsuke</string>

    <string name="noelle_desc">Like most of Mondstadts young people, Noelle always dreamed of being a knight of Favonius when she grew up. She may not have what it takes to be a knight just yet, but she is learning. Working as a maid at the Knights headquarters, she is constantly taking notes on what constitutes knightly speech, knightly conduct, and knightly customs. She holds firm to her belief that one day she will join their ranks, she just needs to keep trying her hardest at everything she does.</string>
    <string name="pang_noelle">Maid of Favonius</string>
    <string name="noelle_birthday">march 21th</string>
    <string name="noelle_affil">Knight of Favonius</string>
    <string name="noelle_vc">Takao Kanon</string>

    <string name="razor_desc">Some say he is an orphan raised by wolves. Others say he is a wolf spirit in human form. He is most at home in the wild, fighting with claw and thunder. To this day the wolf boy can be found prowling the forest, where he and his wolf pack hunt to survive using nothing more than their animal instincts.</string>
    <string name="pang_razor">Wolf Boy</string>
    <string name="razor_birthday">September 9th</string>
    <string name="razor_affil">Wolvendom</string>
    <string name="razor_vc">Uchiyama Kouki</string>

    <string name="sucrose_desc">An alchemist with an insatiable curiosity towards the world and everything in it. Attached to the Knights of Favonius as an assistant to Albedo, her area of focus is "bio-alchemy." She strives to enrich the world by transforming living things with the power of alchemy. Granted, the products of her research sometimes prove to be more weird than wonderful — but on the whole, she has made monumental contributions to the field of bio-alchemy.</string>
    <string name="pang_sucrose">Knight of Favonius alcemist</string>
    <string name="sucrose_birthday">November 26th</string>
    <string name="sucrose_affil">Knight of Favonius</string>
    <string name="sucrose_vc">Fujita Akane</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="combat">Combat Info</string>
    <string name="Talent">Talents</string>

    <string name="bennetbasic">Strike of Fortune</string>
    <string name="bennetbasicdesc">Normal Attack: Performs up to 5 rapid strikes.
Charged Attack: Consumes a certain amount of Stamina to unleash 2 rapid sword swings.

Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground below, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="bennetE">Passion Overload</string>
    <string name="bennetRdesc">Bennett concentrates the spirit of Adventure and Pyro into his blade. Depending on how long he charges for, different effects occur.
Press: A single, swift flame strike that deals Pyro DMG.
Hold (Short): Charges up, resulting in different effects when unleashed based on the Charge Level
Level 1: Strikes twice, dealing Pyro DMG and launching opponents.
Level 2: Unleashes 3 consecutive attacks that deal impressive Pyro DMG, but the last attack triggers an explosion that launches both Bennett and the enemy.
Bennett takes no damage from being launched, but can take fall damage if he falls down a cliff.</string>
    <string name="bennetBurst">Fantastic Voyage</string>
    <string name="bennetBurstdesc">Bennett performs a jumping slam attack that deals Pyro DMG, creating an Inspiration Field for 12 seconds.
Inspiration Field:

If the health of a character within the AoE is equal to or falls below 70%, their health will regenerate each second. The amount of HP restores scales off Bennett\'s Max HP.
If the health of a character within the AoE is higher than 70%, they gain an ATK Bonus that scales based on Bennett\'s Base ATK.
Imbues characters within the AoE with Pyro.</string>

    <string name="albedo_basic">Favonius Bladework</string>
    <string name="Albedo_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Perform up to 5 rapid strikes.
Charged Attack: Consumes a certain amount of Stamina to unleash 2 rapid sword strikes.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground below, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="Albedo_E">Solar Isotoma</string>
    <string name="Albedo_E_desc">Albedo creates a Solar Isotoma using alchemy, which deals AoE Geo DMG on appearance.
Solar Isotoma has the following properties:
When enemies within the Solar Isotoma zone take damage, the Solar Isotoma will generate Transient Blossoms which deal AoE Geo DMG. DMG dealt scales off Albedo\'s DEF. Transient Blossoms can only be generated once every 2s.
When a character is located at the locus of the Solar Isotoma, the Solar Isotoma will accumulate Geo power to form a crystallized platform that lifts the character up to a certain height. Only one crystallized platform can exist at a time.
Solar Isotoma is a Geo Construct.
Hold to designate the location of the skill.</string>
    <string name="Albedo_burst">Tectonic Tide</string>
    <string name="Albedo_burst_desc">Under Albedo\'s command, Geo crystals surge and burst forth, dealing AoE Geo DMG in front of him.
If a Solar Isotoma created by Albedo himself is on the field, 7 Fatal Blossoms will be generated in the Solar Isotoma field, bursting violently into bloom and dealing AoE Geo DMG.
Tecotonic Tide DMG and Fatal Blossom DMG will not generate Transient Blossoms.</string>

    <string name="Amber_basic">Sharpshooter</string>
    <string name="Amber_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Perform up to 5 consecutive shots with a bow.
Charged Attack: Perform a more precise Aimed Shot with increased DMG. While aiming, flames will accumulate on the arrowhead. A fully charged flaming arrow will deal Pyro DMG.
Plunging Attack: Fires off a shower of arrows in mid-air before falling an striking the ground, dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="Amber_E">Explosive Puppet</string>
    <string name="Amber_E_desc">The ever-reliable Baron Bunny takes the stage.
Baron Bunny:

Continuously taunts the enemy, drawing their fire.
Baron Bunny\'s HP scales with Amber\'s Max HP.
When destroyed or when its timer expires, Baron Bunny explodes, dealing AoE Pyro DMG.
Hold: Adjusts the throwing direction of Baron Bunny. The longer the button is held, the further the throw.</string>
    <string name="Amber_burst">Fiery Rain</string>
    <string name="Amber_burst_desc">Fires off a shower of arrows, dealing continuous AoE Pyro DMG.</string>
    
    <string name="diluc_basic">Tempered Sword</string>
    <string name="diluc_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Perform up to 4 consecutive strikes.
Charged Attack: Drains Stamina over time to perform continuous slashes. At the end of the sequence, perform a more powerful slash.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="diluc_E">Searing Onslaught</string>
    <string name="diluc_E_desc">Performs a forward slash that deals Pyro DMG.
This skill can be used 3 times consecutively. Enters CD if not cast again within a short period (5s).</string>
    <string name="diluc_burst">Dawn</string>
    <string name="diluc_burst_desc">Releases intense flames to knock nearby opponents back, dealing Pyro DMG. The flames then converge into the weapon, summoning a Phoenix that flies forward and deals massive Pyro DMG to all opponents in its path. The Phoenix explodes upon reaching its destination, causing a large amount of AoE Pyro DMG.
The searing flames that run down his blade cause it to be infused with Pyro.</string>

    <string name="eula_basic">ladework-Edel</string>
    <string name="eula_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Perform up to five consecutive strikes.
Charged Attack: Drains Stamina over time to perform continuous slashes. At the end of the sequence, perform a more powerful slash.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="eula_E">Icetide Vortex</string>
    <string name="eula_E_desc">Sharp frost, swift blade.
Press: Slashes swiftly, dealing Cryo DMG. When it hits an opponent, Eula gains a stack of Grimheart that stacks up to two times. These stats can only be gained once every 0.3s.
Grimheart: Increases Eula\'s resistance to interruption and DEF.
Hold: Wielding her sword, Eula consumes all the stacks of Grimheart and lashes forward, dealing AoE Cryo DMG to opponents in front of her.
If Grimheart stacks are consumed, surrounding opponents will have their Physical RES and Cryo RES decreased.
Each consumed stack of Grimheart will be converted into an Icewhirl Brand that deals Cryo DMG to nearby opponents.</string>
    <string name="eula_burst">Glacial Illumination</string>
    <string name="eula_burst_desc">Brandishes her greatsword, dealing Cryo DMG to nearby opponents and creating a Lightfall Sword that follows her around for a duration of up to 7s.
While present, the Lightfall Sword increases Eula\'s resistance to interruption. When Eula\'s own Normal Attack, Elemental Skill, and Elemental Burst deal DMG to opponents, they will charge the Lightfall Sword, which can gain an energy stack once every 0.1s.
Once its duration ends, the Lightfall Sword will descend and explode violently, dealing Physical DMG to nearby opponents.
This DMG scales on the number of energy stacks the Lightfall Sword has accumulated.
If Eula leaves the field, the Lightfall Sword will immediately explode.</string>

    <string name="jean_basic">Favonius Bladework</string>
    <string name="jean_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Performs up to 5 consecutive strikes.
Charged Attack: Consumes a certain amount of stamina to launch an opponent using the power of wind. Launched opponents will slowly fall to the ground.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground below, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="jean_E">Gale Blade</string>
    <string name="jean_E_desc">Focusing the might of the formless wind around her blade, Jean releases a miniature storm, launching opponents in the direction she aims at, dealing massive Anemo DMG.
Hold: At the cost of continued stamina consumption, Jean can command the whirlwind to pull surrounding opponents and objects towards her front.
Direction can be adjusted.
Character is immobile during skill duration.</string>
    <string name="jean_burst">Dandelion Breeze</string>
    <string name="jean_burst_desc">Calling upon the wind\'s protection, Jean creates a swirling Dandelion Field, launching surrounding opponents and causing Anemo DMG. At the same time, she instantly regenerates a large amount of HP for all party members. The amount of HP restored scales off Jean\'s ATK.
Dandelion Field:
Continuously regenerates HP of characters within the AoE and continuously imbues them with Anemo.
Deals Anemo DMG to opponents entering or exiting the Dandelion Field.</string>

    <string name="kaeya_basic">Cerebalde</string>
    <string name="kaeya_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Performs up to 5 rapid strikes.
Charged Attack: Consumes a certain amount of Stamina to unleash 2 rapid sword strikes.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground below, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="kaeya_E">Frostgnaw</string>
    <string name="kaeya_E_desc">Unleashes a frigid blast, dealing Cryo DMG to opponents in front of Kaeya.</string>
    <string name="kaeya_burst">Glacial Waltz</string>
    <string name="kaeya_burst_desc">Coalescing the frost in the air, Kaeya summons 3 icicles that revolve 4 times around him for 8 seconds.
These icicles will follow the character around and deal Cryo DMG to opponents in their path for so long as they persist.</string>

    <string name="noelle_basic">Bladework - Maid</string>
    <string name="noelle_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Performs up to 4 consecutive slashes.
Charged Attack: Drains Stamina over time to perform continuous swirling attack on all nearby opponents. At the end of the sequence, performs an additional powerful slash.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground below, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="noelle_E">Breastplate</string>
    <string name="noelle_E_desc">Summons protective stone armor, dealing Geo DMG to surrounding opponents and creating a shield. The shield\'s DMG Absorption scales based on Noelle\'s DEF.
The shield has the following properties:
When Noelle\'s Normal and Charged Attacks hit a target, they have a certain chance to regenerate HP for all characters.
Possesses 150% DMG Absorption efficiency against all Elemental and Physical DMG.
The amount of HP healed when regeneration is triggered scales based on Noelle\'s DEF.</string>
    <string name="noelle_burst">Sweeping Time</string>
    <string name="noelle_burst_desc">Gathering the strength of stone around her weapon, Noelle strikes the opponents surrounding her within a large AoE, dealing Geo DMG.
Afterwards, Noelle gains the following effects:
Larger attack AoE
Converts attack DMG to Geo DMG that cannot be overridden by any other elemental infusion.
Increased ATK that scales based on her DEF.</string>

    <string name="razor_basic">Steel Fang</string>
    <string name="razor_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Perform up to 4 consecutive strikes.
Charged Attack: Drains Stamina over time to perform continuous swirling attacks against all nearby opponents. At end of the sequence, perform a more powerful slash.
Plunging Attack: Plunges from mid-air to strike the ground below, damaging opponents along the path and dealing AoE DMG upon impact.</string>
    <string name="razor_E">Thunder Claw</string>
    <string name="razor_E_desc">Hunts his prey using the techniques taught to him by his master and his Lupical.
Press: Swings the Thunder Wolf Claw, dealing Electro DMG to opponents in front of Razor.
Upon striking an opponent, Razor gains an Electro Sigil, which increases his Energy Recharge rate.
Razor can have up to 3 Electro Sigils simultaneously, and gaining a new Electro Sigil refreshes their duration.
Hold: Gathers Electro energy to unleash a lightning storm over a small AoE, causing massive Electro DMG, and clears all of Razor\'s Electro Sigils. Each Electro Sigil cleared in this manner will be converted into Energy for Razor.</string>
    <string name="razor_burst">Lighning Fang</string>
    <string name="razor_burst_desc">Summons the Wolf Within which deals Electro DMG to all nearby opponents. This clears all of Razor\'s Electro Sigils, which will be converted into elemental energy for him.
The Wolf Within will fight alongside Razor for the skill\'s duration.
The Wolf Within:
Strikes alongside Razor\'s normal attacks, dealing Electro DMG.
Raises Razor\'s ATK SPD and Electro RES.
Causes Razor to be immune to DMG inflicted by the Electro-Charged status.
Disables Razor\'s Charged Attacks.
Increases Razor\'s resistance to interruption.
These effects end when Razor leaves the battlefield.
When Razor leaves the field, a maximum of 10 Energy will be returned to him based off the duration remaining on this skill.</string>

    <string name="sucrose_basic">Wind Spirit</string>
    <string name="sucrose_basic_desc">Normal Attack: Performs up to 4 attacks using Wind Spirits, dealing Anemo DMG.
Charged Attack: Consumes a certain amount of Stamina and deals AoE Anemo DMG after a short casting time.
Plunging Attack: Calling upon the power of her Wind Spirits, Sucrose plunges towards the ground from mid-air, damaging all opponents in her path. Deals AoE Anemo DMG upon impact with the ground.</string>
    <string name="sucrose_E">Astable Anemo</string>
    <string name="sucrose_E_desc">Creates a small Wind Spirit that pulls opponents and objects towards its location, launches opponents within its AoE, and deals Anemo DMG.</string>
    <string name="sucrose_burst">anemo Creation</string>
    <string name="sucrose_burst_desc">Sucrose hurls an unstable concoction that creates a Large Wind Spirit. While it persists, the Large Wind Spirit will continuously pull and launch nearby opponents, and deal Anemo DMG.
Elemental Absorption: If the Wind Spirit comes into contact with Hydro/Pyro/Cryo/Electro elements, it will deal additional elemental DMG of that type. Elemental Absorption may only occur once per use.</string>

    <string name="data_received">Data Diterima</string>

    <string name="heroname">nama Hero</string>
    <string name="herodesc">desc Hero</string>
    <string name="herobirthday">Hero Birthday</string>
    <string name="Herovcname">Hero Voice Character</string>
    <string name="basic">basicattck</string>
    <string name="basicdesc">basicdesc</string>
    <string name="Ename">Ename</string>
    <string name="Edesc">Edesc</string>
    <string name="burst">burst</string>
    <string name="burstdesc">burstdesc</string>

</resources>